[
        {
                "question": "How does Refurbia work?",
                "answer": "You can browse our website or mobile apps, select your device from the list of acceptable items, get instant quote and get paid instantly. You will also be able to buy refurbished as well as new electronic items soon.",
                "sortOrder":"a",
                "redirectUrl":""
        },
        {
                "question": "What types of devices does Refurbia accept?",
                "answer": "We accept a wide range of smartphones from various brands, provided they meet our quality and functional criteria. Please check our app for a detailed list of accepted models.",
                "sortOrder": "b",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "How do I sell my smartphone on Refurbia?",
                "answer": "- Download the Refurbia app or go to Refurbia Website.\n- Enter details about your smartphone.\n- Receive an instant quote.\n- Accept the quote and schedule a pickup.\n- Get paid once the device is inspected and approved.",
                "sortOrder": "c",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "What if my device is not listed on Refurbia?",
                "answer": "Reach out to our customer support team at support@refurbia.in with details about your device. We will update you about your device soon.",
                "sortOrder": "d",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "What is the refurbishment process?",
                "answer": "Our refurbishment process includes:\n- Diagnostic testing to assess the device’s functionality.\n- Replacement of any faulty components.\n- Cleaning and cosmetic improvements.\n- Final testing to ensure the device meets our quality standards.",
                "sortOrder": "e",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "What is the warranty on refurbished devices?",
                "answer": "All refurbished devices come with a 6-month warranty covering any functional defects. Please refer to our warranty policy for more details.",
                "sortOrder": "f",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "How can I escalate an unsolved issue?",
                "answer": "you can reach out to the grievance officer Mr Asif Khan at asif.khan@refurbia.in. Your grievances shall be solved within 48 working hours.",
                "sortOrder": "g",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "How can I ensure my data is safe when selling my phone?",
                "answer": "Before handing your phone to us, we recommend performing a factory reset to erase all personal data. Our refurbishment process includes additional steps to ensure all data is completely wiped from the device.",
                "sortOrder": "h",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "What should I do if the pickup is delayed?",
                "answer": "Reach out to our customer support team at support@refurbia.in, provide your order number and pickup details for quick assistance.\n● Reschedule Pickup: If the delay is significant and you prefer to reschedule, our support team can help you arrange a new pickup time that is convenient for you.",
                "sortOrder": "i",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "Can I trade in multiple devices at once?",
                "answer": "Yes, you can trade in multiple devices. Each device will be evaluated separately, and you will receive individual quotes for each one.",
                "sortOrder": "j",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "How can I delete my Refurbia Account and Data?",
                "answer": "You can contact our customer support team at support@refurbia.in with a request to delete your account. Please include your account details in the email for verification purposes. Once we receive your request, we will process the account deletion and notify you once it’s complete.",
                "sortOrder": "k",
                "redirectUrl": ""
        }
]